显示
Showing
显示加载指示器非常简单。所以这个查询对象
a loading indicator is pretty straight forward. So this query object
有另一个有用的属性，就是正在加载。
has another useful property that is is loading.
我们可以获取它，然后在这里我们可以说
We can grab that and then here we can say
如果正在加载，我们可以返回一个
if is loading we can return a
段落并显示“加载中”。我们还可以渲染一个旋转器。
paragraph and say loading. We can also render a spinner.
现在让我们测试我们的应用程序。所以回到浏览器，刷新，你可以
Now let's test our application. So back in the browser, refresh, you can
看到“加载中”出现得非常快。我们可以模拟一个慢速连接
see loading appearing pretty quickly. We can simulate a slow connection
通过进入网络选项卡并应用一个
by going to the network tab and applying a
限制。所以在这里我们可以模拟一个快速的3G连接。
throttling. So here we can simulate a fast 3G connection.
现在让我们刷新。
Now let's refresh.
很快就会发生。
It's going to happen in a second.
好的，这里是加载中，然后我们得到了数据。这就是
Alright, here's loading and then we get the data. So this is the beauty of
react query的美丽之处。我们不再需要为我们的
react query. We no longer have to declare separate state variables for our
数据、错误和加载状态单独声明状态变量。一切都被很好地处理了。
data, error and the loading state. Everything is well taken care of.